Oh, yeah, have you heard
about the campfire superstition?
That if you confess to your crush,
you'll fall in love?
I know it sounds kinda sketchy.
Yeah, sketchy.
But we're here anyway,
so why don't you try it?
Maybe you'll finally
get an answer from him.
[sighs softly]
[mellow music playing]
[inaudible]
I won't.
Until Taiki actually
falls in love with me,
I don't need an answer.
UEDA SHIKI HOTEL
[girl] I've got it right here.
[boy] Awesome, thanks.
[gasps]
[chuckling]
[wind blowing]
[opening theme song playing]
BLUE BOX
EPISODE 24
A ROLLER COASTER
[Hina] Last night...
[serene music playing]
[Taiki] I'm glad that woman was okay.
[Chinatsu] Yeah, definitely.
[Taiki] It got late, didn't it?
[Hina] I've known about it
from the beginning.
I mean, I knew that Taiki liked Chinatsu
when I confessed to him.
[girl] Hina.
[Hina] This? This is no big deal.
I'll take this one.
Yeah, thanks.
[Hina] It's not like
everything has been this painful.
Like, when I confessed to him,
that deer-in-headlights look he had,
it was priceless.
When I get him to look at me,
as part of the great Hina's strategy,
and his face turns bright red...
some part of me explodes,
and all the little Hinas in my heart
have a dance party.
When we put on Snow White
for the cultural festival...
SNOW WHITE SCRIPT
THE PRINCE KISSES HER
...I fantasized about how it would be
if it were Taiki playing the prince.
[chuckles]
When that actually happened,
I almost went crazy
because of how nervous I was.
But in the end,
I'll never forget our scene together.
[music ends]
There's no way he understands...
that that day...
I couldn't help
but imagine the real thing.
Kissing you for real, Taiki.
What?
[heart beating]
Wanna do it for real?
I really thought
I'd be okay with him kissing me.
In the stillness of that classroom,
I felt hot all over.
My heart was beating so fast, it hurt.
- [Taiki] Hina, watch out!
- Huh?
[Hina] During the play,
I was glad because I didn't want
my first kiss to be onstage.
But after that,
so many people got involved.
I think Taiki's reaction really meant
he was being considerate of me.
But the truth is
I didn't completely hate the rumors.
If anything...
I was hoping they would lead
to the two of us dating.
I wonder how it would feel
to actually date him.
We'd walk home together, go to karaoke,
take a ton of pictures...
We'd even hold hands.
[gasps]
[grunts]
[sighs]
[all screaming]
[Hina] I guess I know now
what it means
to be on an emotional roller coaster.
Why doesn't he date me just to try it out?
He could just use me and see how it goes.
There are times I think like that.
But he's sincere. I like that about him.
He's not that kind of person.
If I asked him those things,
I don't think he could follow through
and hurt his friend so easily.
Meat's not ready yet.
I'm not that big of an eater, come on.
[gasps softly]
You have a leaf in your hair.
Oh? Where is it?
- A bit higher.
- Mmm?
No, it's further back.
[Hina] Further?
Here. Let me help you.
Dang, it's really in there.
I like you.
But if I say that too much,
he'll probably get overwhelmed.
Still...
[chuckles] I got it.
[Hina] You can't win a fight
if you don't throw a punch.
I'll use the relationship we do have.
Look at me.
[grunts softly]
[Hina] I don't wanna be
just his best friend anymore.
It doesn't matter
if it's tomorrow, next week, next month.
I'll wait as long as I have to.
So, for now...
Look, there's one on you too!
Only 'cause
you're trying to put it in my hair!
[chuckles] No. Oh, what's that?
- There's a big bug on you.
- Huh? Huh? Where?
Just kidding.
[Taiki] You get me every time.
Well, would you look at that?
They get along so well.
I've always admired couples
that act like friends with each other.
Moriya, you like to play
with people's hearts, huh?
I wouldn't do something like that.
And even if I did, the people I date
are usually okay with it.
- [sighs]
- When it comes to love,
the person being adored
is the one who's the happiest.
So then, how does the other person
find happiness?
What?
In your love life, you get confessed to,
but your relationships
never last, do they?
I'm sorry, but...
I'm not buying your method.
[Ayame] What?!
WHAT?!
You think you can meddle
from the sideline, Four-eyes?
You don't even have a girlfriend, do you?
[grunts angrily]
I can't believe him!
[boy] This year's camp...
is officially over!
Let's light it!
[all exclaiming]
[girl] It's so pretty!
[lighthearted music playing]
BLEH
Bleh!
[Kyo grunts]
[Ayame scoffs]
[sighs]
I'm not buying your method.
[Ayame] That's what he said.
It is true that my relationships
have never lasted that long.
Not to mention, I don't think
I've ever actually been in love.
That is all the more reason...
'Cause it's actually fun
having a crush on Taiki.
[Ayame] ...to help her!
[upbeat music playing]
Who on this planet
wouldn't want to fight for...
someone who loves with all their heart?
Oh?
It's so cold.
- No jacket?
- Nah.
I left it in the gym earlier.
I'm gonna go grab it.
[giggles]
- Oh, Hina-bean!
- Huh?
We're having a problem
with one of the cables,
but, apparently,
they have some spares back in the gym.
Could you get one for me?
Sure thing.
Oh, really? Thank you!
By the way,
you take as much time
as you need to, girl.
[Hina] Hmm?
Everything okay?
Just getting equipment.
'Cause Ayame asked for my help.
Our manager is really demanding sometimes.
Huh?
I'LL HELP YOU
I wanna help you!
TAKE ALL THE TIME YOU WANT!
Take the time that you need.
[Hina] She set this up.
- [Taiki] What was it you needed?
- Uh...
I can help.
[gasps softly]
It's not here.
[Hina] Hmm.
It's possible Ayame was just
improvising the whole scenario.
[grunts]
[lighthearted music playing distantly]
Look at that.
We have a good view of the campfire.
- Oh, yeah.
- [gasps]
It's even more magical up here.
Oh, of course Nishida's dancing.
Let's watch from here for a while.
[gasps]
Now that you mention it, I am tired.
Why don't we take a break?
[sighs]
[Hina chuckles]
So even the amazing Taiki
who runs nonstop all year round
gets tired too.
You're making fun of me.
The energy I expend
differs from a certain someone
who travels by bus.
I will have you know we ran every morning.
That reminds me.
YAMANONAKA HOTEL
Third year of junior high school,
you snuck out of the hotel
where we were staying on our school trip
for a morning run.
It's part of my routine.
Yeah, but you got in trouble, right?
The teacher only found out
'cause everyone teased me about it.
And remember that time
during the second-year camping trip
where we all played Cops and Robbers?
SMUG
Oh, when I avoided everybody till the end?
SHADOW CLONES
Uh-huh.
All your fancy footwork cracked me up.
Is that a compliment?
Don't think I didn't see you.
How you were the very first one
to get captured
and then had nothing to do.
I got caught 'cause of my shoelaces.
Yeah, okay.
Even a cat knows
it must hide its claws sometimes.
[Taiki laughs]
But you got captured right away
during the second round too.
And you couldn't even tell
that they were trying to let you escape.
[gasps]
[Hina] Hey, Taiki.
[Taiki grunts]
[Hina] There's something I wanna ask you.
[Taiki] What is it?
[Hina] During the King's Card Game...
[Taiki] Uh-huh.
[Hina] What was your actual answer
going to be?
For a minute there, it seemed
you were going to spill the beans
about liking Chinatsu!
But surprisingly,
you're more of a chicken than I thought.
[chuckles softly]
But I guess you're not the kind of guy
who blurts out his feelings like that.
Oh! But of course
you can confess if you want.
That's been our deal from the beginning.
I'm totally fine with that.
I just need to try harder than you.
To be honest,
sometimes all of this stings a bit,
but it's nothing to worry yourself over.
It's all fine because I love you.
[gasps]
[wind blowing]
Welp. Should we head back?
I should tell Ayame
we couldn't find the equipment.
[sighs] Why did I just say that?
I wasn't planning
on telling him I love him.
Hina.
[Hina] Hmm?
Sorry.
[heart beating]
[Hina] You're sorry?
About what?
[wind blowing]
[Taiki] I can't... go out with you.
["Shade of Love"
by Takashi Ohmama playing]
Nuh-uh.
I told you that I don't need an answer.
There's no need to rush it.
It's not as if you and Chinatsu
have started dating, right?
[Taiki] We haven't. But...
[Hina] Exactly. So you don't need
to give me an answer yet.
I'm not going to complain,
no matter how long it takes.
Reject me now,
and then when you come to like me later,
you'll regret it.
Even so,
I don't think
our relationship's working right now.
I know you've said that it's okay
if I go after Chinatsu instead.
But I haven't been able to face her
with honesty
because of this situation.
And even though I like Chinatsu,
I've been swayed by you, and I feel awful.
I think my indecisiveness
is ultimately hurting you, Hina.
That's why
I want to make things clear now.
The two of us should...
I told you that I'm fine with it!
I confessed to you
even though you like someone else.
It may be that you like Chinatsu,
but it doesn't change
the fact that I like you.
That's not how this is supposed to work.
I don't care!
Everything is gonna be worth it
when I get you to like me!
Hina, I don't feel the same way about you.
Why not?
Chinatsu doesn't have
as many memories with you as I do.
Is it 'cause we don't live together?
We can start doing that.
It's not for me to know
how Chinatsu really feels about you.
- But I feel--
- Hina...
The person I like isn't going to change.
[gasps]
[sniffles]
- [sobs]
- Hina...
[song ends]
[humming]
[chuckles] I wonder if things went well.
Just the two of them alone in a gym,
dimly lit by the campfire.
And there was
a superstition or something too.
I bet it set a really romantic mood.
[grunts] Uh?
Hina-bean?
[sobs quietly]
[Ayame] Are you okay?
- Wait, did something--
- [Hina continues sobbing]
[Ayame] She's crying.
He said he can't go out with me.
[gasps]
That he has feelings for someone else.
[mellow music playing]
And even if she doesn't like him back,
that the person he likes
isn't going to change!
[crying]
[Hina] In rhythmic gymnastics,
there are some people
who believe that hard work pays off,
and there are other people
who say that isn't always true.
My hard work has always paid off.
And I've come to like myself
because I've never stopped trying.
[all exclaiming]
[Hina] But...
when it comes to love...
[indistinct chatter, laughter]
[Chinatsu sighs]
[wind blowing]
[Hina sobs]
[bawling]
[Hina] ...why am I so pathetic?
[closing theme song playing]